Guide to the Clifton R. Merritt Papers 1935-2008
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- The American Wilderness Alliance / American Wildlands, 1957-2007; Series IV; 29.5 linear feet
  - Subject Files, 1957-2007; Subseries 2; 20.5 linear feet
    - Entomological Society of America and the National Insect, 1990 (Box-folder 75/13)
    - Environmental Communication Specialists-Don Whittemore and Dawn Amato, 1992 (Box-folder 75/14)
    - Falcons, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 75/15)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs, 1980-1993 (Box-folder 76/1-2)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 76/3)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 76/4)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs, 1994-2003 (Box-folder 76/5)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 76/6)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs-Articles, Clifton R. Merritt, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 76/7)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs-Executive Committee, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 77/1)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs-Executive Committee Minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 77/2)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs-Hazel Wolf Correspondence, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 77/3)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs-News Articles and Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 77/4)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs-Newsletters, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 77/5)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs-Newsletters, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 77/6)
    - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs-Outdoors West, 1984-2006 (Box-folder 77/7)
    - Field Advisory Group on Effectiveness of Wilderness Management, 1990 (Box-folder 77/8)
    - Fire in Wilderness, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 77/9)
    - Fire Policy, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 77/10)
    - Fires of 1988, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 77/11)
    - First American Energy-Westland Wind Project, 2004 (Box-folder 77/12)
    - Flat Tops Wilderness, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 77/13)
    - Flathead National Forest, 1969-1987 (Box-folder 77/14)
    - Flathead National Forest-North Fork Valley, 1982 (Box-folder 77/15)
    - Flathead National Forest-Wild and Scenic Rivers, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 78/1-3)
    - Flathead River, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 78/4)
    - Flint Creek Range-Deerlodge National Forest, 1982-1997 (Box-folder 78/5)
    - Forest Economics Clippings, 1994 (Box-folder 78/6)
    - Forest Fires, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 78/7)
    - Forest History Articles, 1986-2001 (Box-folder 78/8)
    - Forest Service 75th Anniversary Award, 1980 (Box-folder 78/9)
    - Forest Service Moratorium on Roads in Roadless Areas, 1998 (Box-folder 78/10)
    - Forest Service News, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 78/11)
    - Forest Service Partnership with Outfitters, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 78/12)
    - Forever Wild, 1983 (Box-folder 78/13)
    - Forever Wild Endowment, 1986 (Box-folder 78/14)
    - Forever Wild Endowment, 1986-2001 (Box-folder 78/15)
    - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness-Commercial Outfitters and Guides Lawsuit, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 78/16)
    - Fred Burr Waster User Association, 1990 (Box-folder 78/17)
    - Frenchman Creek Roadless Area, 1999 (Box-folder 78/18)
    - Frenchmen Creek-Bureau of Land Management, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 78/19)
    - Friend of the Westslope Cutthroat Trout, circa 2002 (Box-folder 78/20)
    - Friends of the Wild Swan, 1996-2005 (Box-folder 78/21)
    - Michael Frome, Correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 79/1)
    - Gallatin National Forest, 1966-1984 (Box-folder 79/2)
    - Gallatin National Forest, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 79/3)
    - Gallatin National Forest, 1986-1997 (Box-folder 79/4)
    - Gallatin National Forest, 2002 (Box-folder 79/5)
    - Gallatin National Forest-Jack Creek, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 79/6)
    - Gallatin National Forest-Robert E. Breazeale Supervisor, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 79/7)
    - Game Farms, 1994-2002 (Box-folder 79/8)
    - Gila Lower Box and Blue Creek Wilderness Study Area, 1987 (Box-folder 79/9)
    - Glacier Clippings, 1998 (Box-folder 79/10)
    - Glacier National Park, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 79/11)
    - Grant-Kohrs Ranch Historic Site-Deerlodge National Forest, 1980 (Box-folder 79/12)
    - Great Bear Foundation, 2001 (Box-folder 79/13)
    - Great Smoky Mountains, 1990 (Box-folder 79/14)
    - Great Western Trail, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 79/15)
    - Greater Salmon-Selway Ecosystem, 1987 (Box-folder 79/16)
    - Greater Yellowstone Coalition, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 79/17-18)
    - Greater Yellowstone Coalition, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 80/1)
    - Greater Yellowstone Coalition, undated (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem, 1987 (Box-folder 80/3)
    - Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem Grant Proposal, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 80/4)
    - Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem Grant Proposal-Steele and Reese, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 80/5)
    - Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem-Bald Eagle Habitat, 1987 (Box-folder 80/6)
    - Green and Yampa Rivers-Colorado River Drainage, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 80/7)
    - Grizzly Bear Metapopulations, 1994 (Box-folder 80/8)
    - Grizzly Bear Recovery-Salmon-Selway Grizzly Coalition, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 80/9)
    - Halting Road building-Proposals, Memos, Correspondence, 1986-2002 (Box-folder 80/10-11)
    - Tom Harding, Correspondence, 1997 (Box-folder 80/12)
    - Dan Heinz, Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 80/13)
    - Helena National Forest, 1973-1985 (Box-folder 80/14)
    - Helena National Forest, 1995 (Box-folder 80/15)
    - Hells Canyon National Recreation Area-Oregon and Idaho, 1986-1996 (Box-folder 80/16)
    - Hells Canyon Preservation Council, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 80/17)
    - Hells Canyon-Oregon and Idaho, 1993 and undated (Box-folder 80/18)
    - High Uintas, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 80/19)
    - High Uintas Preservation Council, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 81/1)
    - Rick Hill, Representative from Montana-Conservation Concerns, 1996 (Box-folder 81/2)
    - History of the Scapegoat Wilderness and Montana Wilderness Study Areas, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 81/3)
    - Holy Cross Wilderness, 1987 (Box-folder 81/4)
    - Holy Cross Wilderness (Homestake II Project-Colorado), 1987 (Box-folder 81/5)
    - HR 631, Colorado Wilderness Bill, 1993 (Box-folder 81/6)
    - Humane Society Newsletter, 1996 (Box-folder 81/7)
    - Humbug Spires-Montana, 1985 (Box-folder 81/8)
    - Hunter Organizations and Newsletters, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 81/9)
    - Hyalite-Porcupine-Buffalo Horn Proposed Wilderness Study Area, Gallatin National Forest, 1983-1996 (Box-folder 81/10)
    - Hyalite-Porcupine-Buffalo Horn, Statement-Clifton Merritt, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 81/11)
    - Hyalite-Porcupine-Buffalo Horn Wilderness Study Area, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 81/12)
    - Hyalite-Porcupine-Buffalo Wilderness Study Area, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 81/13)
    - Idaho, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 81/14-16)
    - Idaho Alternative Wilderness-Roadless Area Review II, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 81/17)
    - Idaho Environmental Council, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 81/18)
    - Idaho Environmental Council Newsletter, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 81/19)
    - Idaho Outfitter Lawsuit, 1987 (Box-folder 81/20)
    - Idaho Outfitters-Wilderness Caches, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 82/1)
    - Idaho Wilderness, 1988 (Box-folder 82/2)
    - Idaho Wilderness Bill, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 82/3)
    - Idaho Wilderness Bill, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 82/4)
    - Idaho Wilderness Bill, 1991 (Box-folder 82/5)
    - Idaho Wilderness Bill, undated (Box-folder 82/6)
    - Idaho Wilderness Bills, 1993 (Box-folder 82/7)
    - Inland Empire Public Lands Council, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 82/8)
    - Inland Empire Public Lands Council-Dr. John Osborn, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 82/9-11)
    - Interim Colorado Wilderness Bill-Senator Tim Wirth, 1990 (Box-folder 82/12)
    - Interior Columbia Basin Ecosystem Management Project, 1997 (Box-folder 82/13)
    - Interior Committee Schedules, 1987 (Box-folder 82/14)
    - Interview in Western Outdoors on the American Wilderness Alliance, 1985 (Box-folder 82/15)
    - Jewel Basin, 1983-2004 (Box-folder 82/16)
    - Jewel Basin Proposed Wilderness Study Area, Flathead National Forest, 1968-1983 (Box-folder 82/17-18)
    - Kootenai and Lolo Wilderness Accords, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 83/1)
    - Kootenai National Forest, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 83/2)
    - Kootenai National Forest, 1995 (Box-folder 83/3)
    - Kreck, Dr. Loren, Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 83/4)
    - Land Use Planning Flow Chart-Wilderness, undated (Box-folder 83/5)
    - Las Cruces/Lordsburg Resource Area, 1987 (Box-folder 83/6)
    - Last Refuge Project-Montana's Wilderness Legends, 2000 (Box-folder 83/7)
    - Laws, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 83/8)
    - Lee Metcalf Celebration, 2002 (Box-folder 83/9)
    - Lee Metcalf Wilderness Alliance, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 83/10)
    - Lee Metcalf Wilderness Alliance, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 83/11)
    - Lewis and Clark National Forest, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 83/12)
    - Lewis and Clark National Forest, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 83/13)
    - Lifescapes, 1996 (Box-folder 83/14)
    - Limekiln Canyons Wilderness Study Area, 1980 (Box-folder 83/15)
    - Limits of Acceptable Change Fish and Wildlife Plan, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 83/16)
    - Lincoln-Scapegoat Correspondence, Notes and Clippings, 1980-2003 (Box-folder 83/17)
    - Little Blackfoot, 1983 (Box-folder 83/18)
    - Lolo, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 83/19)
    - Lolo and Rattlesnake National Forests, 1983 (Box-folder 83/20)
    - Lolo National Forest, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 83/21)
    - Lolo National Forest, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 83/22)
    - Lolo National Forest Plan, 1982-1996 (Box-folder 83/23)
    - Dr. John Loomis, Natural Resource Economist, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 83/24)
    - Lost Trail Powder Mountain, 1996 (Box-folder 83/25)
    - Jerry Mallett, Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 83/26)
    - Jerry Mallett, Election-Sportsmen in Colorado, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 83/27)
    - David McCargo, Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 83/28)
    - Melcher, et. Al, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 84/1)
    - Clifton Merritt, Notes and Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 84/2)
    - Clifton Merritt, Newsletter Article about, 2007 (Box-folder 84/3)
    - Clifton Merritt, Remarks on Wilderness, 1999 (Box-folder 84/4)
    - Clifton Merrtt, Speeches, 1968-1988 (Box-folder 84/5)
    - Clifton Merritt, Speeches, etc., 1968-2000 (Box-folder 84/6-7)
    - Donna Metcalf, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 84/8)
    - Lee Metcalf, Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 84/9)
    - Middle Fork Flathead, 1980 (Box-folder 84/10)
    - Middle Fork of the Flathead, Correspondence and Articles, 1969-2005 (Box-folder 84/11)
    - Middle Fork of the Judith-Wilderness Study Area, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 84/12)
    - Mineral Policy Center, 1996 (Box-folder 84/13)
    - Mining, 1981 (Box-folder 84/14)
    - Mining Claims-Montana Wilderness, 1996 (Box-folder 84/15)
    - Mining on Public Lands, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 84/16)
    - Mining Reform, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 84/17)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 84/18)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 84/19)
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 85/1)
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters-Montana Wilderness, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 85/2)
    - Miscellaneous Wilderness Articles, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 85/3)
    - Miscellaneous Wilderness Organizations' Newsletters, 1987-2005 (Box-folder 85/4)
    - Miscellaneous Wilderness Organizations' Newsletters and Mailers, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 85/5)
    - Mission Mountains Tribal Wilderness, 1981 (Box-folder 85/6)
    - Mission Mountains Tribal Wilderness, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 85/7)
    - Missouri Breaks Wilderness, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 85/8)
    - Missouri River Breaks National Monument, 2003 (Box-folder 85/9)
    - Montana Alternative "W" (Citizens' Wilderness Proposal), 1984 (Box-folder 85/10)
    - Montana Blackfoot River and Mining, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 85/11)
    - Montana Bureau of Land Management, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 85/12)
    - Montana Bureau of Land Management Bear Trap Canyon, 1980 (Box-folder 85/13)
    - Montana Bureau of Land Management Lewistown District, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 85/14)
    - Montana Bureau of Land Management Wilderness Proposals, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 86/1)
    - Montana Bureau of Land Management Wilderness Review, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 86/2)
    - Montana Bureau of Land Management Wilderness Review, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 86/3)
    - Montana Bureau of Land Management-Sleeping Giant Wilderness Area, undated (Box-folder 86/4)
    - Montana Clippings, 1977-1994 (Box-folder 86/5)
    - Montana Conservation Voters, 2001 (Box-folder 86/6)
    - Montana General, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 86/7-8)
    - Montana Guides and Outfitters, 1981-1994 (Box-folder 86/9)
    - Montana National Forests, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 86/10)
    - Montana Natural Areas System, 1987 (Box-folder 86/11)
    - Montana Outfitter Guests, 1986 (Box-folder 86/12)
    - Montana Project, 1990 (Box-folder 86/13)
    - Montana Proposed Highways Through Wilderness, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 86/14)
    - Montana Proposed Wilderness Maps, 1985 and undated (Box-folder 86/15)
    - Montana River Action, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 86/16)
    - Montana Special Alerts, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 86/17)
    - Montana State Bills, 1995 (Box-folder 86/18)
    - Montana State Lands and Montana Law Board, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 86/19)
    - Montana Wilderness, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 86/20)
    - Montana Wilderness, 1987 (Box-folder 86/21)
    - Montana Wilderness, 1987-2005 (Box-folder 86/22)
    - Montana Wilderness Act Correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 87/1)
    - Montana Wilderness Association, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 87/2)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1975-1993 (Box-folder 87/3)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 87/4-5)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 87/6)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 87/7-9)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1990 (Box-folder 87/10)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1991 (Box-folder 87/11)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1984, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 87/12)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1988-Senator Melcher (Box-folder 87/13)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1989, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 88/1)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1990, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 88/2)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1991, S. 1696, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 88/3)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1993, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 88/4)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1994 (Box-folder 88/5)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, Baucus, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 88/6)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, HR 2090, Representative Pat Williams, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 88/7)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, Summaries, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 88/8)
    - Montana Wilderness Bills, 1968-1987, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 88/9)
    - Montana Wilderness Clippings, 1969-1998 (Box-folder 88/10)
    - Montana Wilderness Correspondence, 1982-1992 (Box-folder 88/11)
    - Montana Wilderness Designation Book-Lerna Naegele, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 88/12)
    - Montana Wilderness Issues, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 89/1-2)
    - Montana Wilderness Issues, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 89/3-4)
    - Montana Wilderness Maps, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 89/5)
    - Montana Wilderness News Clippings, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 89/6)
    - Montana Wilderness Status Map, 1981 (Box-folder 89/7)
    - Montana Wilderness Study Act, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 89/8-10)
    - Montana Wilderness Study Act, 1975-2004 (Box-folder 89/11)
    - Montana Wilderness Study Act, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 89/12)
    - Montana Wilderness Study Act, S. 393, 1977-2006 (Box-folder 89/13)
    - Montana Wilderness Study Act, S. 393, Metcalf, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 90/1)
    - Montana Wilderness Study Act, Lawsuit, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 90/2)
    - Montana Wilderness Study Areas, Clippings, 1995-2004 (Box-folder 90/3)
    - Montana Wilderness-Bureau of Land Management, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 90/4)
    - Montana Wildlands Coalition, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 90/5)
    - Montana Wildlife Management, 1982-2001 (Box-folder 90/6)
    - National Conservation Area-Law and Bill, 1991 (Box-folder 90/7)
    - National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA) Documents-Bitterroot National Forest, 1998 (Box-folder 90/8)
    - National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA) Documents-Wise River District-Beaverhead-Deerlodge National Forest, 1997 (Box-folder 90/9)
    - National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA)-American Wildlands Overview, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 90/10)
    - National Forest Management Act, 1999 (Box-folder 90/11)
    - National Forest Protection and Restoration Act, 1997 (Box-folder 90/12)
    - National Forest Road Policy, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 90/13)
    - National Forests, 1995 (Box-folder 90/14)
    - National Forests, 1996 (Box-folder 90/15)
    - National Parks and Monuments, 1995 (Box-folder 90/16)
    - National Parks and Monuments, 1999 (Box-folder 90/17)
    - National Scenic and Historic Trails, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 90/18)
    - National Wetlands Inventory, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 90/19)
    - National Wild and Scenic and Rivers, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 90/20)
    - National Wild and Scenic and Rivers, undated (Box-folder 90/21)
    - National Wilderness Preservation System, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 90/22)
    - National Wilderness System, 1962-1986 (Box-folder 90/23-25)
    - National Wildlife Refuges, undated (Box-folder 90/26)
    - Native Ecosystem Council, 1998 (Box-folder 90/27)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2004 (Box-folder 91/1)
    - Natural Resources Laws and Public Lands Protection Conference, 1999 (Box-folder 91/2)
    - Nevada, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 91/3)
    - Nevada Outdoor Recreation Association, 1987-1996 (Box-folder 91/4)
    - Nevada Outdoor Recreation Association-Bureau of Land Management Grants, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 91/5)
    - Nevada Wilderness Bill-Friends of Nevada Wilderness, 1987-2000 (Box-folder 91/6)
    - New Mexico Wilderness, 1987 (Box-folder 91/7)
    - New York, 1987 (Box-folder 91/8)
    - News Articles, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 91/9)
    - Northern Rockies Bioregion, undated (Box-folder 91/10)
    - Northern Rockies Bioregion and Montana Wilderness, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 91/11)
    - Northern Rockies Bureau of Land Management Task Force, 1990-2004 (Box-folder 91/12)
    - Northern Rockies Bureau of Land Management Wilderness Issues, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 91/13-15)
    - Northern Rockies Ecosystem Protection Act (NREPA), 1991-1994 (Box-folder 91/16)
    - Northern Rockies Ecosystem Protection Act (NREPA)-Alliance for the Wild Rockies, 1999 (Box-folder 91/17)
    - Northern Rockies Ecosystem Protection Act (NREPA)-Booklets before Congress, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 92/1)
    - Northern Rockies Task Force-Montana Wilderness, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 92/2-3)
    - Northern Rockies Wilderness Issues, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 92/4)
    - Northern Yellowstone Rim-Montana Issue, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 92/5)
    - Northwest-General Information, 1987 (Box-folder 92/6)
    - Notes, 2003 and undated (Box-folder 92/7)
    - Notes-Clifton Merritt, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 92/8)
    - Notes-Clifton Merritt, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 92/9)
    - Off-road vehicle and snowmobile use on Public Lands, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 92/10)
    - Oil and Gas Leasing in Wilderness, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 92/11)
    - Oil and Gas Leasing on the Rocky Mountain Front, 1997 (Box-folder 92/12)
    - Oral Hearing and Appeal Highlights on the South Fork of the Flathead River Management Decision, 1987 (Box-folder 92/13)
    - Oregon, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 93/1)
    - Oregon Natural Desert Association, 1989 (Box-folder 93/2)
    - Oregon Rivers Council, 1987 (Box-folder 93/3)
    - Other Montana Rivers, 1995 (Box-folder 93/4)
    - Pacific Crest Trail Conference, 1988 (Box-folder 93/5)
    - Partnership Information, 2000 (Box-folder 93/6)
    - Pew Environmental Research Center, 2001 (Box-folder 93/7)
    - Pew Wilderness Center, Doug Scott, 2001 (Box-folder 93/8)
    - Pike and San Isabel National Forests, 1987 (Box-folder 93/9)
    - Pinchot Institute for Conservation, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 93/10)
    - Pintler-Anaconda Wilderness-Montana, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 93/11)
    - Pioneer Skills Award Program-Bill Worf, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 93/12)
    - Predator Support, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 93/13)
    - Proposed Centennial Mountains Wilderness, 1985-1999 (Box-folder 93/14-16)
    - Proposed Garnet Range Wilderness, 1998 (Box-folder 93/17)
    - Proposed Great Burn Wilderness, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 94/1)
    - Proposed Great Divide Wilderness-Montana and Idaho, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 94/2)
    - Proposed Lee Metcalf Wilderness, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 94/3)
    - Proposed Sleeping Child Wilderness, undated (Box-folder 94/4)
    - Proposed Sleeping Child Wilderness-Bureau of Land Management, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 94/5-6)
    - Proposed Wilderness Study Additions-Western Montana, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 94/7-8)
    - Publicity-Newspapers, Texas-San Antonio Light, 1981 (Box-folder 94/9)
    - Rangeland Management, 1994 and undated (Box-folder 94/10)
    - Sally Ranney, 1997 (Box-folder 94/11)
    - Sally Ranney-Award Nomination, 1995 (Box-folder 94/12)
    - Rattlesnake Wilderness, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 94/13)
    - Rattlesnake Wilderness, Lolo National Forest, 1980 (Box-folder 94/14)
    - Ravalli County Fish and Wildlife Association, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 94/15)
    - Ravalli Republic Interview, 2003 (Box-folder 94/16)
    - Recommended Actions for Governmental Agencies to Mitigate Risk and Discover Cause of Observed Symptoms in People and Wildlife in the Bitterroot Valley, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 94/17)
    - Reports on Garnet Range Roadless Area as Potential Wilderness Areas-Bill Cunningham, 1998 (Box-folder 94/18)
    - Resource Specialist/Wildlife Biologist Position-American Wildlands, 1994 (Box-folder 94/19)
    - Response to Robert Dreher's Report on the Oral Hearing for the Montana Wilderness Association regarding the Flathead River Management Plan, 1987 (Box-folder 94/20)
    - Review of the Bitterroot Final Forest Plan and Environmental Impact Statement, 1985 (Box-folder 95/1)
    - River Monitor, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 95/2)
    - Rivers-Denver Water, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 95/3)
    - Road building Moratorium in Roadless Areas, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 95/4)
    - Roadless Area Review (RARE) III, 1987 (Box-folder 95/5)
    - Roadless Area Review II-Buffalo Peaks-San Isabel National Forest, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 95/6)
    - Roadless Area Reviews and Evaluations, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 95/7-8)
    - Roadless Rule, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 95/9)
    - Rock Creek, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 95/10)
    - Rock Creek -Lolo, and Deerlodge National Forests, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 95/11)
    - Rocky Mountain Elk Foundation, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 95/12)
    - Rocky Mountain Front, 1996-2004 (Box-folder 95/13)
    - Rocky Mountain Front, 2002 (Box-folder 95/14)
    - Rocky Mountain Front, 2004 (Box-folder 95/15)
    - Rocky Mountain Front-Proposed Addition to the Bob Marshall-Scapegoat Wilderness, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 96/1)
    - Rupert Cutler Articles, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 96/2)
    - Salvage Logging, 1994-2002 (Box-folder 96/3)
    - Sample Letters to Representatives and Senators, 1992 (Box-folder 96/4)
    - San Juan National Forest, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 96/5)
    - Santa Fe Gold Environmental Assessment-Elkhorn Mountains, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 96/6)
    - Sapphire Crest Wilderness, 1978-1996 (Box-folder 96/7)
    - Sapphire Wilderness Study Area, 1977-2003 (Box-folder 96/8)
    - Sapphire Wilderness Study Area, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 96/9)
    - Sapphire Wilderness Study Area and Stony Mountain, 2005 (Box-folder 96/10)
    - Saylor, Congressman John P., Correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 96/11)
    - Scapegoat Enlargement-Helena, Lolo, and Lewis and Clark National Forests Proposed Wilderness Study Areas, 1987-2005 (Box-folder 96/12)
    - Scapegoat Wilderness Anniversary, 2002 (Box-folder 96/13)
    - Scapegoat Wilderness Area, 2002 (Box-folder 96/14)